Last update: 02/09/2023



Sergio **Betancor Bello**



+34 601 28 37 36



Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Spain



serbetancor@gmail.com



<u>linkedin.com/in/sergio-betancor-</u> bello

ABOUT ME

I was born on August 16, 2000 (23 years old) in Canary Islands, Spain. I am in my final year of a doble degree in Business and Computer Science. My year of experience living in Warsaw helped me to get to know more than 10 European countries and to receive a full year of lecturing in English.

This has given me an open-minded attitude towards working in any country. My hobbies and interests include sports, reading and researching/developing algorithms.

STRENGTHS

- > Teamwork
- Adaptability to new situations
- Problem-solving
- Understanding of the business and IT environment

WEAKNESSES

- Lack of creative development
- Predominance of theoretical over practical concepts

EDUCATION

2018-present **Doble Degree in Business and**

Computer Science

Las Palmas of Gran Canaria

University

2021-2022 **Erasmus+**

Warsaw University of Technology

LANGUAGES

✓ Spanish: Native language

✓ English: Level B2 (Cambridge University, 2016)

✓ German: Level B1 (Official Language School of Telde, 2018)

WORK HISTORY

2019-2021 Freelance teacher
Teacher of primary, secondary and high school students

Eventors

2018-2019 **Eventopro**

Assembly and dismantling of stages for audiovisual productions

addiovisual productions

2018 Canarias Masterclass Program

Mentored by PWC in the Canarias
Masterclass program → First contact with

consulting and accounting projects

2017 **Summer Program**Monitor assistant